<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mirella van Teulingen</title>
    <link>http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl</link>
    <description>This is my personal blog where I write about things I come across while coding and the meetings/conferences I attended. Most articles are related to front end development.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
        
        
    
        
        
            <item>
                <title>CSS Day 2013</title>
                <description>
                     <![CDATA[Friday 14 june in Amsterdam I attended the CSSDay conference. Eight experts talked about 8 different CSS modules. The focus was on techniques of these modules we might not know about and the future of CSS. During the conference I learned that CSS is in very active development. It was an incredible, informative and awesome day. An high standard conference I've ever attended so far. I hope that there will be another one within 1 or 2 years.]]>
                </description>
                <pubDate>
                    16-06-2013
                </pubDate>
                <link>
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/cssday2013
                </link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/cssday2013
                </guid>
            </item>
        
    
        
        
            <item>
                <title>Customize Sublime text editor</title>
                <description>
                     <![CDATA[At the Fronteers conference 2012 in Amsterdam, Addy Osmani used Sublime Text Editor in his presentation. The editor looked really interesting. Right after the conference I installed Sublime and looked around for packages which would make my life as front end developer easier and make editing more fun. This article is a small tutorial with tips to configure Sublime to your needs, a list of interesting packages, how to customize a theme and links to useful documentation.]]>
                </description>
                <pubDate>
                    12-02-2014
                </pubDate>
                <link>
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/customize-sublime
                </link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/customize-sublime
                </guid>
            </item>
        
    
        
        
            <item>
                <title>Django form customization using Crispy Forms</title>
                <description>
                     <![CDATA[At Dreamsolution we regularly use Crispy Forms to generate  complex forms in Django. I want to share some practical customization examples with Crispy Forms using the formhelper API.]]>
                </description>
                <pubDate>
                    21-09-2014
                </pubDate>
                <link>
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/customize-django-crispy-forms
                </link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">
                    http://www.mirellavanteulingen.nl/blog/customize-django-crispy-forms
                </guid>
            </item>
        
    
  </channel>
</rss>